[
    {
      "question": " Which of the following is generally used for performing tasks like creating the structure of the relations, deleting relation ?",
  
      "option1": " DML(Data Manipulation Language",
  
      "option2": " Query",
  
      "option3": " Relational Schema",
  
      "option4": " DDL(Data Definition Language)",
  
      "answer": " DDL(Data Definition Language)"
},
    {
        "question": " Which of the following provides the ability to query information from the database and insert tuples into, delete tuples from, and modify tuples in the database ?",
    
        "option1": " DML(Data Manipulation Language)",
    
        "option2": " DDL(Data Definition Language)",
    
        "option3": " Query",
    
        "option4": " Relational Schema",
    
        "answer": " DML(Data Manipulation Language)"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which one of the following given statements possibly contains the error?",
    
        "option1": " select * from emp where empid = 10003;",
    
        "option2": " select empid from emp where empid = 10006;",
    
        "option3": " select empid from emp;",
    
        "option4": " select empid where empid = 1009 and Lastname = 'GELLER';",
    
        "answer": " select empid where empid = 1009 and Lastname = 'GELLER';"
      },
      {
        "question": " What do you mean by one to many relationships ? ",
    
        "option1": " One class may have many teachers",
    
        "option2": " One teacher can have many classes",
    
        "option3": " Many classes may have many teachers",
    
        "option4": " Many teachers may have many classes",
    
        "answer": " One teacher can have many classes"
      },
      {
        "question": " A Database Management System is a type of _________software.",
    
        "option1": " It is a type of system software",
    
        "option2": " It is a kind of application software",
    
        "option3": " It is a kind of general software",
    
        "option4": " Both A and C",
    
        "answer": " It is a type of system software"
      },
      {
        "question": " The term 'FAT' is stands for_____",
    
        "option1": " File Allocation Tree",
    
        "option2": " File Allocation Table",
    
        "option3": " File Allocation Graph",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " File Allocation Table."
      },
      {
        "question": "  Which of the following can be considered as the maximum size that is supported by FAT ?",
    
        "option1": " 8GB",
    
        "option2": " 4GB",
    
        "option3": " 4TB",
    
        "option4": " None of the above",
    
        "answer": " 4GB"
      },
      {
        "question": " The term 'NTFS' refers to which one of the following ?",
    
        "option1": " New Technology File System",
    
        "option2": " New Tree File System",
    
        "option3": "New Table type File System",
    
        "option4": " Both A and C",
    
        "answer": " New Technology File System"
      },
      {
        "question": "  Which of the following can be considered as the maximum size that is supported by NTFS ?",
    
        "option1": " 4GB",
    
        "option2": " 16TB",
    
        "option3": " 64TB",
    
        "option4": " 8TB",
    
        "answer": " 4GB"
      },
      {
        "question": " A huge collection of the information or data accumulated form several different sources is known as ________:",
    
        "option1": " Data Management",
    
        "option2": " Data Miningc",
    
        "option3": " Data Warehouse",
    
        "option4": " Both B and C",
    
        "answer": " Data Warehouse"
      }
    
    
    
]